<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Cédric Ho Thanh on Cédric HT</title><link>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/</link><description>Recent content in Cédric Ho Thanh on Cédric HT</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://cedric.hothanh.fr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About me</title><link>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/about/</guid><description>I am currently a postdoctoral researcher at Prof. Takemasa Miyoshi&amp;rsquo;s Prediction Science Laboratory, RIKEN Cluster for Pioneering Research, in the Medical Data Deep Learning Team, headed by Dr. Jun Seita. I am also a member of the RIKEN Quantum group.
I obtained my PhD in mathematics from Paris University, France, in October 2020, where I was a student at the Research Institute for Foundations of Computer Science (IRIF), under the supervision of Pierre-Louis Curien (IRIF) and Samuel Mimram (LIX, École Polytechnique).</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/contact/</guid><description>eMail cedric.hothanh [At sign] riken [ccTLD of Japan] Address Nihonbashi 1-chome Mitsui Building, 15th floor, 1-4-1 Nihonbashi, Chuo-ku, Tokyo 103-0027, Japan or 〒 103-0027 東京都 中央区日 本橋 1-4-1 日本橋一丁目 三井ビルディング 15 階</description></item><item><title>Research</title><link>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/research/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/research/</guid><description>Articles and preprints Trust your neighbours: Handling noise in multi-objective optimisation using kNN-averaging, 2023, with Stefan Klikovits, Ahmet Cetinkaya, and Paolo Arcaini. In Applied Soft Computing
Topological recurrence theorems for infinitary probabilistic model checking, 2022, with Natsuki Urabe and Ichiro Hasuo.
Frenetic at the SBST 2021 tool competition, 2021, with Ezequiel Castellano, Ahmet Cetinkaya, Stefan Klikovits, Xiaoyi Zhang, and Paolo Arcaini. In IEEE/ACM 14th International Workshop on Search-Based Software Testing (SBST).</description></item><item><title>Stuff'n things</title><link>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/stuff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/stuff/</guid><description>Projects Turbo Broccoli: A Python package containing JSON (de)serialization extensions. It makes it possible to embed bytes, numpy arrays, keras models, etc. in a dict and seemlessly pass it on to json.dump, and conversely, reconstruct these objects using json.load.
kappak: My LaTeX package. It regroups functionalities I find useful, from general style of LaTeX documents (title page, chapter style, header / footer, …), to more specific math related commands (theorem environments, commutative diagrams, …).</description></item><item><title>Teaching</title><link>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/teaching/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/teaching/</guid><description>TA Introduction à la Programmation Java (Introduction to Java Programming), freshmen in computer science, University of Paris, 2020 Automates et Analyse Lexicale (Automata and Lexical Analysis), sophomores in computer science, University of Paris, 2019 Initiation à la Programation C (Introduction to C Programming), freshmen in preparatory classes for engineering school (CPEI), University of Paris, 2019 Initiation à la Programmation Java (Introduction to Java Programming), freshmen in computer science, University of Paris, 2018 Analyse de Données Structurées (Introduction to Compiler Construction), sophomores in computer science, University of Paris, 2018 Initiation à la Programmation Python (Introduction to Python Programming), freshmen in MIASHS (math, computer science, and social sciences), University of Paris, 2017 Algèbre Linéaire Avancée (Advanced Linear Algebra), freshmen in mathematics, EPFL, 2015 Mathématiques (Mathematics), freshmen in architecture, EPFL, 2012 &amp;amp; 2013 &amp;amp; 2014 Programation en C++ (Programming in C++), freshmen in mathematics, physics, and biology, EPFL, 2013 &amp;amp; 2014 Algèbre Linéaire Avancée (Advanced Linear Algebra), freshmen in physics, EPFL, 2014 Analyse (Calculus), freshmen in mechanical engineering, EPFL, 2013 Mathématiques Générales (General Mathematics), freshmen in biology and pharmaceutical sciences, University of Lausanne (UNIL), 2012 Supervised projects Faridath Akinotcho: λ-calcul.</description></item></channel></rss>