<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Cédric Ho Thanh on Cédric HT</title><link>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/</link><description>Recent content in Cédric Ho Thanh on Cédric HT</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://cedric.hothanh.fr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About me</title><link>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/about/</guid><description>I am currently a postdoctoral researcher at Prof. Takemasa Miyoshi&amp;rsquo;s Prediction Science Laboratory, RIKEN Cluster for Pioneering Research, Japan.
I obtained my PhD in mathematics from Paris University, France, in October 2020, where I was a student at the Research Institute for Foundations of Computer Science (IRIF), under the supervision of Pierre-Louis Curien (IRIF) and Samuel Mimram (LIX, École Polytechnique). There, I was a member of PPS team (IRIF) and πr2 team of the National Institute for Research in Computer Science and Control (INRIA).</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/contact/</guid><description>eMail cedric.hothanh [At sign] riken. [ccTLD of Japan] Address Nihonbashi 1-chome Mitsui Building, 15th floor, 1-4-1 Nihonbashi, Chuo-ku, Tokyo 103-0027, Japan or 〒103-0027 東京都 中央区日 本橋1-4-1 日本橋一丁目 三井ビルディング 15階</description></item><item><title>Research</title><link>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/research/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/research/</guid><description>Articles and preprints Topological recurrence theorems for infinitary probabilistic model checking, 2022, with Natsuki Urabe and Ichiro Hasuo. Submitted.
Trust your neighbours: handling noise in multi-objective optimisation using kNN-averaging, 2021, with Stefan Klikovits, Ahmet Cetinkaya, and Paolo Arcaini. Submitted.
Frenetic at the SBST 2021 tool competition, 2021, with Ezequiel Castellano, Ahmet Cetinkaya, Stefan Klikovits, Xiaoyi Zhang, and Paolo Arcaini. In IEEE/ACM 14th International Workshop on Search-Based Software Testing (SBST).</description></item><item><title>Stuff'n things</title><link>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/stuff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cedric.hothanh.fr/stuff/</guid><description>Programming kappak: My LaTeX package. It regroups functionalities I find useful, from general style of LaTeX documents (title page, chapter style, header / footer, …), to more specific math related commands (theorem environments, commutative diagrams, …). Consequently, it might not be as useful for you as it is for me, but you are welcome to give a try. Wiki-that-might-or-might-not-be-up-to-date (￣ω￣;).
s3backup: This docker image performs incremental backups of a given volume to an S3 storage using restic and rclone.</description></item></channel></rss>